A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 2: McLean Citizens Association Administrative and Subject Files, 1914-2010
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - MCA Flyers and Publicity Material, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - MCA Membership Information and Lists, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes and Citizen of the Year, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - MCA Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - MCA Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings on McLean Topics, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - MCA Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings on McLean Topics (McLean Central Park revitalization, playgrounds, and Betty Cooke's "Pink House" preservation), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - MCA Bylaws Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - MCA Flyer "Stop the Real Estate Tax Increase", 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - MCA Treasurer's Report, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - MCA Bylaws Amendments, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - MCA Bylaws Adopted, 2002 December 4 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - MCA Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - MCA Bylaws Revision Resolutions, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - MCA Citizen of the Year Award, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MCA Bylaws, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - MCA Policies and Procedures Manual (Draft), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - MCA Bylaws Adopted, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee - The West Group, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee - Spring Hill Sector, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - MCA Policies and Procedures Manual (Draft), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - MCA Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - MCA Treasurer's Report, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - MCA Resolution on Public Safety Bond Issue, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - MCA Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - MCA Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - MCA Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - MCA Resolutions, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - MCA Citizen of the Year Award to Lilla Richards, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - MCA Correspondence (Lilla Richards, Frank Campbell, and Robert Jackson RE: car tax and related issues), 2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Lilla Richards Emails on Local Issues, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - MCA Committee Reports, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - MCA Minutes, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - MCA Committee Reports, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - MCA Stationary, Calendars, etc. (blank), Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Series 3: McLean Citizens Foundation Administrative Records, 1975-2014
  - MCF History, 1979-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - MCF Brochures, 1984-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - MCF Founding Initial Contracts (Evans Farm Inn), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - MCF Bylaws, 1978? (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - MCF Articles of Incorporation, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - MCF Board of Trustees, 1980-2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - MCF Grants Policy and Application Requirements, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - MCF Project Processing Procedure, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - MCF Grants, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - MCF Bylaws (as given to the McLean Citizens Association), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - MCF Bylaws, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - MCA Property Sales (established MCF's financial basis), 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings on Specific Grants, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - MCF Challenge Grant Agreement, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - MCF - Similar Organizations, 1980, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - MCF Financial Policies, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - MCF Questionnaire, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - MCF IRS Organization Status, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity (Ted Grey - Emerson Gallery), 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity (includes Tree Committee Report), 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - MCF Development Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - MCF Brochure, 1984? (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - MCF Party, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - MCF Turkey Run Pavillions (Claude Moore Farm), 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1985, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - MCF Bench Project, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - MCF Bus Project [photographs of the presentation ceremony], 1985 November (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - MCF Brochure, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - MCF Bosé Audubon Center, Fairfax Audubon Society, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - MCF Langley Development, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - MCF Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - MCF Challenge Grant McLean Project for the Arts, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - MCF McLean Community Center Balcony Pledge [photographs of the presentation ceremony], 1975-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - MCF Grant Neighborhood Watch Computer, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity [photographs of MFC officers at a restaurant with Lilla Richards], 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - MCF Grant to McLean Little League, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity [group photograph], 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - MCF Northern Virginia Community Foundation Papers, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda; Candidates Night, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - MCF Mission Statement, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - MCF WORD Project, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - MCF McLean Women's Center [Photograph of Audrey Moore, Judith Mueller, Suzanne H. Paciulli, and Lilla Richards], 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - MCF McLean Organizations, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - MCF Survey Questionnaires, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - MCF Grants - Expansion of Haycock Community Park, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - MCF Contact Lists for McLean Organizations, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - MCF Grants - Hospice Center of Northern Virginia, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - MCF Newspaper Articles, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - MCF Open House Party, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - MCF Mailings, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - MCF Grants - Pro-File Computer Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - MCF Grants - Family Respite Center, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - MCF Grants - Falls Church-McLean Children's Center, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - MCF Fundraiser, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - MCF Mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - MCF Grants - Family Respite Center, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - MCF Party Costs, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - MCF SEF Matching Gifts, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - MCF Grants Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - MCF Grants - McLean Project for the Arts, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - MCF Grants - Langley Crew Boosters Club, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - MCF Committee Questionnaire, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - MCF Gifts and Pledges, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - MCF Nonprofit Rules, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - MCF Grants - McLean High School, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - MCF Minutes and Agenda, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - MCF Grants - Langley Crew Boosters Club, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - MCF Correspondence, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - MCF Grants - Majiro Society for International Exchange, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - MCF Flyers, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - MCF Grants - Franklin Sherman Playground, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - MCF Fundraising, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - MCF Turkey Run Farm Information, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - MCF Board Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - MCF Boards of Directors Rosters, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - MCF Family Respite Center, Falls Church, Virginia, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - MCF Board Minutes, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - MCF Vinson Hall Correspondence, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - MCF Grants - Haycock Playground, 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - MCF McLean Land Conservancy, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - MCF Open Meetings Information, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - MCF ABC Banquet License, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - MCF Grants, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - MCF Grants - Churchill Road Elementary School PTA Application for Additions to the School Playground Area and Fields, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - MCF Gazebo in McLean Central Park [photo], 2000 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - MCF Grants - Longfellow Middle School, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - MCF Lilla Richards Correspondence with Patricia D. Bragg, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - MCF Open House Report, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings and Photographs, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - MCF Grants - Hospice and Palliative Care of Metropolitan Washington, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - MCF Cardinal Wealth Services Investment Proposal, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - MCF Fidelity Personal Trust Investment Strategy Recommendation, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - MCF Morgan Stanley Dean Witter Investment Proposal, ca. 2000 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - MCF Bank of America Presentations for the McLean Citizens Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - MCF Contact and Invitation Lists, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - MCF Friends of McLean Community Center, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - MCF Stationary, Undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - MCF Treasurer’s Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - MCF Mount Royal Park and Friends of Mount Royal Park, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - MCF Handouts and Related Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - MCF Pimmit Run Stream Valley Trail, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - MCF Grants, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - MCF Project WORD, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - MCF Bylaws and Amendments, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - MCF Grants - McLean High School Ball Field Lights, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - MCF Grants - McLean High School Band Sound System, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - MCF Clemyjontri Park, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - MCF Grants - McLean Community Center Theater Lighting, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - MCF Northern Virginia Conservation Trust, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - MCF Friends of the Community Center, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - MCF Grants Policy, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - MCF Holiday Party, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - MCF Lilla Richards Correspondence with Robert R. Belair RE: Youth Sports in McLean, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - MCF McLean Youth Orchestra, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - MCF Grants - Spring Hill and Bull Neck Parks, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - MCF Grants - Cooper Middle School; one photograph of five people including Lilla Richards, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - MCF McLean Central Park and Friends of McLean Central Park, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - MCF Board Minutes and Agenda, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - MCF Grants - McLean Community Center Indoor Signage (declined), 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - MCF Correspondence of Lilla Richards, Edward Eiches, and Willim J. Byrnes, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - MCF McLean Youth Soccer, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - MCF McLean Central Park Donation of $10,000 from Jean Schiro-Zavella and Vance S. Zavella, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - MCF Lilla Richard's Material on Vietnam Veteran Nurse Lynda Van Devanter Buckley, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - MCF Annual Report (May 2001) and Publicity Report (April 9, 2002), 2001, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - MCF Board Address Lists, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - MCF Grants - Falls Church McLean Children's Center, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - MCF Grants - McLean Central Park Gazebo, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - MCF Grants - Alzheimer's Family Day Center, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - MCF Annual Report to the State Corporation Commission, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - MCF Grants - SHARE Application, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - MCF McLean Little League Registration Handbook, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - MCF Covance/Karloid Meeting (Loretta Scott), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - MCF McLean Land Conservancy, Correspondence and Documents, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - MCF Brochure, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - MCF Merrril-Lynch, Correspondence and Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - MCF Bylaws and Changes (and MCA reaction), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - MCF Nominating Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - MCF 25th Anniversary, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings and Photographs, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - MCF Miscellaneous Correspondence and Materials, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - MCF Publicity and Promotional Material [photographs], 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - MCF Board Minutes and Agenda, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - MCF Grants and Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - MCF Board Minutes and Agenda, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - MCF Treasurer's Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - MCF Bylaws, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - MCF Annual Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - MCF Business Strategy, 2006 November (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - MCF Index of MCF Minutes (1998-2006), 2006 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - MCF Newspaper Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - MCF Correspondence, Lilla Richards' Comments on Name Change to McLean Community Foundation, 2014 October 20 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Series 4: Evans Farm Controversy Files, 1969-2000 (bulk 1998-2000)
  - Fairfax County Board of Zoning Appeals: Complaint about Sales of Pesticides and Fertilizers at Evans Farm Inn, 1969 August 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Board of Zoning Appeals: Evans Farm Inn, Inc., (Zoning applications for additions to the property), 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - MCA Evans Farm Fund Final Disbursement and Donor Lists, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "Save Evans Farm Fund" 1998 Contributors, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Correspondence on Evans Farm, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Evans Farm Board of Zoning Appeals Applications, 1944, 1956, 1974 (photocopies from BZA minutes), Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Save Evans Farm Website Printouts, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Save Evans Farm Petitions (photocopies), ca. 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dranesville District Task Force, ca. 1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Lilla Richards Correspondence on Evans Farm, 1995-1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Save Evans Farm Bumper Sticker, Stickers, and Printing Receipts, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Save Evans Farm Flyers, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Evans Farm History Materials, Undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Burling Tract History, Undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Evans Farm Rezoning, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Evans Farm Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Evans Farm Notes, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation and Evans Farm, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Evans Farm - Katherine K. Hanley and James Zook Correspondence, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Binder, West Group. "Concept and Design References for Evans Farm, McLean, Virginia ", 1998 July 18 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Save Evans Farm Challenge Grant Report to McLean Citizens Foundation, Donations Correspondence, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Resolution for the McLean Land Conservancy, Inc., 2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Lawsuits of Evans Farm Inn and Mohammed Moosavi, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Evans Farm Rezoning Application and Testimony (copies), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Evans Farm - Letters to Planning Commission RE: Rezoning (Includes a chain of title to the property with the original farmhouse), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Planning Commission Information on Evans Farm Inn, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors Public Hearing on Evans Farm, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County Planning Commission Public Hearing Verbatim Transcripts, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Planning Commission Meetings on Evans Farm; Notes and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Ralph B. Evans Correspondence Regarding Evans Farm (copies), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Coalition to Save Evans Farm "Capitulation Letter", 1999 May 10 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Evans Farm Correspondence and Newspaper Articles, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Evans Farm Correspondence, Proposals, Newspaper Articles, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Evans Farm Newspaper Clippings, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Evans Farm Newspaper Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation "Save Evans Farm" Correspondence, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." A-Z Retained for MCF Pres/Open Space Use (RESTRICTED FILE: PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." A-E Retained for Charitable Use. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." F-L Retained for Charitable Use. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." M-R Retained for Charitable Use. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." S-Z Retained for Charitable Use. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." A-Z Refunds. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Retained for Pres/Open Space Use (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Retained for Charitable Use. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Refunds. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Refunds Returned as Undeliverable. (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Donor Cards A-M (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Donor Cards N-Z (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation Donation Records for "Save Evans Farm." Donor Cards (RESTRICTED FILE WITH PHOTOCOPIES OF PERSONAL CHECKS & SIGNATURES), 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Series 5: McLean Planning Committee Files, 1967-2001
  - MPC Bylaws and History (Includes Bylaws of the McLean Business and Professional Association and McLean Landowners Association, Inc.), 1971-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - MPC McLean Task Force Questionnaire, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - MPC Stationary, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - MPC Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - MPC Brochure: McLean: A New Town Center in Historic Fairfax County ca.1968 (photocopy), Undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - MPC Transportation Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - MPC Design Standards (Includes: "Design Standards, McLean, Virginia, Central Business District" and "Economic Conditions and Potentials in the McLean Central Area."), 1970-1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - MPC Area II Plan Changes, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - MPC Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - MPC Bylaws, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - MPC McLean Central Business District PDH, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - MPC Minutes and Correspondence (Theodore Gray material)), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - MPC Fairfax County Board of Supervisors Clerk's Board Summary, 1985 July (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - MPC Master Plan Recommendations, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - MPC Correspondence with Nancy Falck, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - MPC RFP Subcommittee Meeting, 1985 September 23 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - MPC Minutes and Agenda, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - MPC RFP Subcommittee Goals, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - MPC Newspaper Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - MPC Member Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - MPC Meetings, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - MPC Brochures Proposal (Contains several brochures from nearby VA and MD communities but no final brochure for MPC), 1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)